myitthings.com 2012-06-30

# MyItThings - User Generated Magazine - Privacy

MyItThings.com Privacy Policy

**About MyItThings.com**  
MyItThings.com is an online magazine and publishing application that allows our writers to set up unique personal pages that can be linked through different magazine sections on the MyitThings.com website (the “Site”). MyItThings members can view each others' profiles, communicate with other writers on the magazine, share items and photos, post articles and comments, and describe their interests. To enrich our members' experience, we request and display some personal information to other members and visitors, which allows our users to identify each other. MyItThings writers can change their profile information at any time.   
MyItThings.com cares about online privacy If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@myitthings.com](mailto:privacy@myitthings.com). 

**Information Collection and Use by MyItThings.com**   
MyItThings.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and date of birth to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the MyItThings.com service. MyItThings.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, zip code, city and country of residence in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. 

MyItThings.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP addresses, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the Site.  This data is used to manage the Site, track usage and improve the services made available on the Site. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes 

User profile information including members' pictures, writer names, birthday date and country of residence are displayed in order to facilitate user interaction in the MyItThings.com magazine community. Email addresses are used for the purpose of inviting new friends to join MyItThings.com, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within user's personal network. Users communicate on MyItThings.com with each other through the MyItThings.com service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, MyItThings.com allows users to search for other members using their submitted information. 

From time to time, MyItThings.com or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on the Site. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply. 

**Use of Cookies**  
MyItThings.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information for various purposes, including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletters, advertising and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.  Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.  However, you must enable the cookies on your browser in order to use most functions on the Site.  

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by MyItThings.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by MyItThings.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Links**  
MyItThings.com contains links to sites. MyItThings.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on MyItThings.com. 

**User Page**   
Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to your personal page on the Site or any other user page, that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications. 

**Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**  
MyItThings.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info. Please note that once user content has been published on one of the magazine main pages - this content won't be available for user's modifications. 

**Security**  
MyItThings.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords.  MyItThings.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on MyItThings.com, please contact us a [privacy@myitthings.com](mailto:privacy@myitthings.com)

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information MyItThings.com Personal Information**  
Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, MyItThings.com will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by MyItThings.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the MyItThings.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. MyItThings.com reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of MyItThings.com or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. 

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**  
From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy.  If we make changes, we will post them on our Site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the Site after those changes have been posted.  If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that which is stated hereunder at the time of collection, we will notify our users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please contact us at: [privacy@myitthings.com ](mailto:privacy@myitthings.com)
